Diego Morin - Frontend Developer

♥ Venezuela ■ diego.morin321@gmail.com 🛘 +584123266310 🛅 in/diegomorin30/

SUMMARY

I am a Front-End developer with more than 2 years of experience. I have participated in the entire software lifecycle, collaborating with other areas to analyze, desing, and implement the necessary software, always thinking about scalability

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

GAO Inversiones

October 2022 - Present, Miranda - Venezuela

- · . I was in charge of creating a new architecture to improve perfomance
- · Define timelines and tasks for the team, review PR's and assist other enigers

Full Stack Developer

911 Carrizal Venezuela

January 2023 - April 2023, Carrizal Venezuela

- · Designed and developed interfaces for both the login and user management of the 911 database.
- · Created a modal that enabled users to generate and submit tickets to the competent entity of the case, including a checklist and other functionalities.
- $\cdot \ \, \text{Utilized APIs to ensure proper transmission of information between different components of the system}.$

PROJECTS

Personal Portfolio

https://diegom30.github.io/portafolio/ • January 2023 - April 2023

• My portfolio was built using React and incorporates technologies such as Three.js, Tailwind, and Styled Components. With it, I aimed to showcase my skills in web development, as well as my ability to create aesthetically pleasing and functional user interfaces. I also included some of my notable projects to highlight my technical expertise in action. Overall, my portfolio is a demonstration of my dedication to developing high-quality software solutions and my passion for creating unique and memorable user experiences.

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering

IUTA · Miranda Venezuela · 2021

SKILLS

Front End: React, Vainilla JS, SASS, Tailwind

Back End: Java